<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Travel Agency</string>

    <string name="menu1">Explore</string>
    <string name="menu2">Hotels</string>
    <string name="menu3">Trips</string>
    <string name="menu4">Exchange</string>
    <string name="menu5">Profile</string>

    <!-- Onboarding -->
    <string name="onboarding_skip">Skip</string>

    <string name="onboarding1_title_top">Discover the Spirit</string>
    <string name="onboarding1_title_bottom">of Almaty</string>
    <string name="onboarding1_description">
        Discover top destinations and book exclusive tours to explore the nature and culture of Almaty.
    </string>

    <string name="onboarding2_title_top">Comfort &amp;</string>
    <string name="onboarding2_title_bottom">Adventure</string>
    <string name="onboarding2_description">
        Find the best hotels and book exciting tours to experience the true hospitality of Almaty.
    </string>

    <string name="onboarding3_title_top">Unforgettable</string>
    <string name="onboarding3_title_bottom">Journeys</string>
    <string name="onboarding3_description">
        Immerse yourself in the majestic mountains and vibrant city life of Kazakhstans cultural capital.
    </string>

    <string name="onboarding4_title_top">Smart</string>
    <string name="onboarding4_title_bottom">Exchange</string>
    <string name="onboarding4_description">
        Stay updated with real-time currency rates and easily calculate exchanges for your trip.
    </string>

    <string name="onboarding_next_arrow">-></string>
    <string name="onboarding_get_started">Get Started</string>

    <!-- Profile -->
    <string name="profile_title">Profile</string>
    <string name="language_label">Language</string>
    <string name="language_kazakh">Қазақ тілі</string>
    <string name="language_russian">Русский язык</string>
    <string name="language_english">English</string>
    <string name="current_language_name">English</string>
    <string name="dialog_language_title">Choose language</string>

    <!-- Example words (English) -->
    <string name="example_greeting">Hello</string>
    <string name="example_welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="example_thanks">Thank you</string>
    <string name="example_greeting_kk">Сәлем</string>
    <string name="example_greeting_ru">Привет</string>
    <string name="example_greeting_en">Hello</string>

    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="personal_info">Personal info, documents</string>
    <string name="payment_methods">Payment Methods</string>
    <string name="help_support">Help &amp; Support</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>

    <!-- Explore -->
    <string name="explore_title">Explore</string>
    <string name="weather_loading">Almaty • Loading…</string>
    <string name="weather_format">Almaty • %1$s %2$s</string>
    <string name="weather_error">Almaty • —</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Find places, hotels, tours…</string>
    <string name="popular_destinations">Popular Destinations</string>
    <string name="see_all">See All</string>
    <string name="browse_categories">Browse Categories</string>
    <string name="category_citylife">CityLife</string>
    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_spiritual">Spiritual</string>
    <string name="filter_by">Filter by: %1$s</string>
    <string name="this_weekend">This Weekend</string>
    <string name="weekend_tag_cultural">CULTURAL</string>
    <string name="weekend_event_title">Almaty Apple Festival</string>
    <string name="weekend_event_details">Sat, 10:00 AM • First President Park</string>
    <string name="toast_apple_festival">Almaty Apple Festival details</string>

    <!-- Popular Places -->
    <string name="place_1_title">Shymbulak Resort</string>
    <string name="place_1_subtitle">25 min • Mountain Resort</string>
    <string name="place_1_about">Shymbulak Resort is the largest ski resort in Kazakhstan, located in the scenic Ile-Alatau mountains near Almaty. It offers modern ski lifts, well-maintained slopes, and stunning panoramic views. In winter, it is a popular destination for skiing and snowboarding, while in summer visitors enjoy hiking and mountain activities. The resort sits at an altitude of over 2,200 meters above sea level. It is one of the most famous tourist attractions in the country.</string>
    <string name="place_2_title">Kok Tobe Hill</string>
    <string name="place_2_subtitle">City Center • Entertainment</string>
    <string name="place_2_about">Kok Tobe Hill is a well-known viewpoint located on the outskirts of Almaty. Visitors can reach the top by cable car, enjoying breathtaking views of the city and surrounding mountains. At the summit, there are restaurants, souvenir shops, and a small amusement park. It is also home to the famous Beatles monument. Kok Tobe is especially beautiful in the evening when the city lights shine below.</string>
    <string name="place_3_title">Big Almaty Lake</string>
    <string name="place_3_subtitle">1 hr drive • Scenic Nature</string>
    <string name="place_3_about">Big Almaty Lake is a stunning alpine lake situated about 15 kilometers south of Almaty. It is famous for its bright turquoise water, which changes color depending on the season. The lake lies at an altitude of approximately 2,500 meters above sea level. Surrounded by mountain peaks, it offers spectacular natural scenery. It is a popular destination for nature lovers and photographers.</string>
    <string name="place_4_title">Charyn Canyon</string>
    <string name="place_4_subtitle">3 hrs drive • National Park</string>
    <string name="place_4_about">Charyn Canyon is often compared to the Grand Canyon because of its dramatic rock formations. It is located about 200 kilometers east of Almaty. The canyon stretches for over 150 kilometers along the Charyn River. Its most famous section is the "Valley of Castles," known for unique and colorful rock shapes. Charyn Canyon is one of Kazakhstan\'s most impressive natural landmarks.</string>
    <string name="place_5_title">Almaty Central Mosque</string>
    <string name="place_5_subtitle">City Center • Historic</string>
    <string name="place_5_about">Almaty Central Mosque is one of the largest mosques in Kazakhstan. It is located near the Green Bazaar in the center of Almaty. The mosque was opened in 1999 and can accommodate up to 7,000 worshippers at a time. Its white marble walls and large golden dome make it very impressive. Today, it is an important religious and cultural center for Muslims in the city.</string>
    <string name="place_6_title">Medeu Rink</string>
    <string name="place_6_subtitle">20 min drive • Sports Complex</string>
    <string name="place_6_about">Medeu Rink is a high-altitude outdoor ice skating rink located in the mountains near Almaty. It sits at 1,691 meters above sea level, making it one of the highest skating rinks in the world. Medeu is famous for hosting international speed skating competitions and setting world records. In winter, both professionals and visitors come to skate here. The surrounding mountain landscape makes it a unique and beautiful sports venue.</string>
    <string name="place_7_title">Green Bazaar</string>
    <string name="place_7_subtitle">City Center • Market</string>
    <string name="place_7_about">Green Bazaar is one of the oldest and most popular markets in Almaty. It is the perfect place to experience local culture and traditional Kazakh cuisine. Visitors can buy fresh fruits, vegetables, meat, spices, and national sweets. The market is lively and colorful, attracting both locals and tourists. It offers a true taste of everyday life in Almaty.</string>

    <!-- Tags -->
    <string name="tag_skiing">Skiing</string>
    <string name="tag_hiking">Hiking</string>
    <string name="tag_nature">Nature</string>
    <string name="tag_cable_car">Cable Car</string>
    <string name="tag_city_views">City Views</string>
    <string name="tag_lake">Lake</string>
    <string name="tag_photography">Photography</string>
    <string name="tag_adventure">Adventure</string>
    <string name="tag_architecture">Architecture</string>
    <string name="tag_history">History</string>
    <string name="tag_ice_skating">Ice Skating</string>
    <string name="tag_sports">Sports</string>
    <string name="tag_food">Food</string>
    <string name="tag_culture">Culture</string>
    <string name="tag_shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="tag_exhibits">Exhibits</string>

    <!-- Browse by Category -->
    <string name="browse_citylife_title">CityLife &amp; Culture</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_all">All</string>

    <string name="browse_filter_museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_parks">Parks</string>

    <string name="browse_mall">Malls</string>
    <string name="browse_entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_shopping">Shopping</string>

    <string name="browse_filter_mountains">Mountains</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_lakes">Lakes</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_canyons">Canyons</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_city_parks">City Parks</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_botanical">Botanical</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_family">Family</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_mosques">Mosques</string>
    <string name="browse_filter_cathedrals">Cathedrals</string>
    <string name="browse_button_map">Map</string>
    <string name="browse_button_details">Details</string>

    <!-- CityLife destinations -->
    <string name="place_8_title">Zenkov Cathedral</string>
    <string name="place_8_subtitle">Panfilov Park, Almaty</string>
    <string name="place_8_about">A stunning wooden Orthodox church located in Panfilov Park. It is one of the tallest wooden buildings in the world and a symbol of Almaty. Built without nails, the cathedral features colorful architecture and is surrounded by the Eternal Flame and 28 Panfilov heroes memorial.</string>
    <string name="place_9_title">Central State Museum</string>
    <string name="place_9_subtitle">Samal-1, Almaty</string>
    <string name="place_9_about">One of the largest museums in Central Asia, showcasing the history and culture of Kazakhstan. The museum houses archaeological finds, ethnographic collections, and exhibits from ancient times to the present day. The building itself is an architectural landmark with a distinctive blue dome.</string>

    <string name="place_101_title">Green Bazaar</string>
    <string name="place_101_subtitle">City Center • Traditional Market</string>
    <string name="place_101_about">Green Bazaar is one of the oldest and most authentic markets in Almaty. Visitors can find fresh fruits, spices, traditional Kazakh products, and local delicacies. It is a vibrant place where tourists can experience the true atmosphere of the city. The market is located near Panfilov Park and is a must-visit cultural spot.</string>

    <string name="tag_market">Market</string>
    <string name="tag_food2">Local Food</string>
    <string name="tag_local">Local Culture</string>

    <string name="place_102_title">Esentai Mall</string>
    <string name="place_102_subtitle">Luxury • Shopping and Dining</string>
    <string name="place_102_about">Esentai Mall is a premium shopping destination in Almaty featuring international luxury brands, fine dining restaurants, and a modern cinema. It offers a high-end shopping experience in a stylish and comfortable environment. The mall is popular among tourists and locals seeking quality leisure time.</string>

    <string name="tag_luxury">Luxury</string>
    <string name="tag_entertainment">Entertainment</string>

    <string name="place_103_title">Dostyk Plaza</string>
    <string name="place_103_subtitle">Modern Mall • Shopping and Cinema</string>
    <string name="place_103_about">Dostyk Plaza is a modern shopping center offering a wide range of international brands, cafes, and a cinema complex. Its contemporary design and convenient location make it a popular destination for shopping and entertainment in Almaty.</string>

    <string name="tag_mall">Mall</string>
    <string name="tag_cinema">Cinema</string>

    <string name="place_104_title">Mega Center Almaty</string>
    <string name="place_104_subtitle">Large Mall • Family Friendly</string>
    <string name="place_104_about">Mega Center Almaty is one of the largest shopping malls in the city. It offers numerous shops, restaurants, a cinema, and entertainment areas for families. It is a popular destination for both shopping and weekend leisure activities.</string>

    <string name="tag_family">Family</string>

    <string name="place_105_title">Forum Almaty</string>
    <string name="place_105_subtitle">Urban Mall • Modern Lifestyle</string>
    <string name="place_105_about">Forum Almaty is a stylish shopping and lifestyle center located in the heart of the city. It features fashion stores, restaurants, cafes, and entertainment facilities. The mall combines urban design with a comfortable shopping atmosphere.</string>

    <string name="tag_modern">Modern</string>
    <string name="place_106_title">Asia Park</string>
    <string name="place_106_subtitle">Shopping Center • Local Brands</string>
    <string name="place_106_about">Asia Park is a convenient shopping center offering a variety of local and international stores. It is popular among residents for everyday shopping and casual entertainment. The mall provides a relaxed and accessible atmosphere.</string>

    <string name="place_107_title">Almaty Arena</string>
    <string name="place_107_subtitle">Sports and Concert Venue</string>
    <string name="place_107_about">Almaty Arena is a large modern sports and concert complex hosting international events, ice shows, and music concerts. It is one of the main entertainment venues in the city and attracts thousands of visitors.</string>

    <string name="tag_events">Events</string>

    <string name="place_108_title">Palace of the Republic</string>
    <string name="place_108_subtitle">Concert Hall • Cultural Events</string>
    <string name="place_108_about">The Palace of the Republic is one of Almaty’s most iconic concert halls. It hosts major cultural events, performances, and festivals. Located near Kok-Tobe, it is a key venue for national and international artists.</string>

    <string name="tag_concerts">Concerts</string>


    <string name="place_109_title">Auezov Kazakh Drama Theatre</string>
    <string name="place_109_subtitle">National Theatre • Drama</string>
    <string name="place_109_about">Auezov Kazakh Drama Theatre is one of the most prestigious cultural institutions in Kazakhstan. It presents classical and modern performances in the Kazakh language and plays a significant role in preserving national theatre traditions.</string>

    <string name="tag_theatre">Theatre</string>


    <string name="place_14_title">Issyk Lake</string>
    <string name="place_14_subtitle">1 hr • Mountain Lake</string>
    <string name="place_14_about">Issyk Lake is located in the Issyk Gorge and is known for its peaceful atmosphere and scenic mountain landscape. It is popular for day trips and picnics.</string>

    <string name="tag_picnic">Picnic</string>

    <string name="place_15_title">Kapchagay Reservoir</string>
    <string name="place_15_subtitle">1 hr • Lakeside отдых</string>
    <string name="place_15_about">Kapchagay Reservoir is a popular summer destination with beaches, resorts, and water activities. It is perfect for swimming and relaxation.</string>

    <string name="tag_beach">Beach</string>
    <string name="tag_water">Water Activities</string>

    <string name="place_17_title">Turgen Gorge</string>
    <string name="place_17_subtitle">1.5 hr • Mountain Gorge</string>
    <string name="place_17_about">Turgen Gorge is famous for its waterfalls, forests, and scenic hiking trails. It is a popular destination for outdoor lovers.</string>

    <string name="tag_waterfall">Waterfall</string>


    <string name="place_18_title">Tamgaly Tas</string>
    <string name="place_18_subtitle">2 hr • Rock Carvings</string>
    <string name="place_18_about">Tamgaly Tas is an open-air site featuring ancient Buddhist rock carvings along the Ili River. It combines природная красота and historical significance.</string>

    <string name="tag_petroglyphs">Petroglyphs</string>


    <string name="place_19_title">Panfilov Park</string>
    <string name="place_19_subtitle">City Center • Historic Park</string>
    <string name="place_19_about">Panfilov Park is one of the most historic green spaces in Almaty. It is home to memorial monuments and is a popular place for walking and relaxation in the city center.</string>

    <string name="tag_walks">Walking</string>
    <string name="tag_citypark">City Park</string>

    <string name="place_20_title">First President Park</string>
    <string name="place_20_subtitle">South Almaty • Modern Park</string>
    <string name="place_20_about">First President Park is a spacious and beautifully landscaped park with fountains, walking paths, and mountain views. It is popular for evening walks and public events.</string>

    <string name="tag_fountain">Fountains</string>

    <string name="place_21_title">Central Park of Culture and Leisure</string>
    <string name="place_21_subtitle">City Park • Family Recreation</string>
    <string name="place_21_about">Central Park is a large recreational area with a lake, amusement rides, спортивные площадки, and walking zones. It is one of the most visited parks in Almaty.</string>

    <string name="tag_attractions">Attractions</string>

    <string name="place_22_title">Almaty Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="place_22_subtitle">Botanical • Green Collection</string>
    <string name="place_22_about">Almaty Botanical Garden features a diverse collection of plants, trees, and flowers. It is a peaceful place for прогулки and enjoying nature inside the city.</string>

    <string name="tag_botanical">Botanical</string>


    <string name="place_23_title">Japanese Garden</string>
    <string name="place_23_subtitle">Decorative Garden • Calm Atmosphere</string>
    <string name="place_23_about">Japanese Garden is a small but beautiful landscaped park with traditional design elements, ponds, and quiet paths for relaxation.</string>

    <string name="tag_garden">Garden</string>
    <string name="tag_relax">Relax</string>

    <string name="place_24_title">Baum Grove</string>
    <string name="place_24_subtitle">Urban Forest • Natural Area</string>
    <string name="place_24_about">Baum Grove is a natural forest zone within Almaty, offering shade, свежий воздух, and walking trails away from busy streets.</string>

    <string name="tag_forest">Forest</string>

    <string name="place_25_title">Fantasy World</string>
    <string name="place_25_subtitle">Amusement Park • Family Fun</string>
    <string name="place_25_about">Fantasy World is an amusement park with rides and entertainment attractions suitable for children and adults.</string>

    <string name="tag_amusement">Amusement Park</string>


    <string name="place_26_title">Almaty Zoo</string>
    <string name="place_26_subtitle">Zoo • Wildlife Experience</string>
    <string name="place_26_about">Almaty Zoo hosts a wide variety of animals and offers educational programs for visitors. It is a popular destination for families with children.</string>

    <string name="tag_animals">Animals</string>
    <string name="tag_education">Education</string>


    <string name="place_27_title">Halyk Arena</string>
    <string name="place_27_subtitle">Ice Arena • Sports and Events</string>
    <string name="place_27_about">Halyk Arena is a modern sports complex that hosts ice skating, хоккей games, and large public events.</string>


    <string name="place_29_title">Baiken Mosque</string>
    <string name="place_29_subtitle">Modern Mosque • Peaceful Atmosphere</string>
    <string name="place_29_about">Baiken Mosque is known for its elegant modern design and calm atmosphere. It is a popular place for prayer and quiet reflection.</string>

    <string name="place_30_title">Nur Mubarak Mosque</string>
    <string name="place_30_subtitle">Islamic University Mosque</string>
    <string name="place_30_about">Nur Mubarak Mosque is located near the Islamic University and combines traditional Islamic design with educational significance.</string>

    <string name="tag_islamic">Islamic</string>


    <string name="tag_cathedral">Cathedral</string>


    <string name="place_32_title">St. Nicholas Cathedral</string>
    <string name="place_32_subtitle">Orthodox Cathedral</string>
    <string name="place_32_about">St. Nicholas Cathedral is an important православный church in Almaty, known for its traditional architecture and peaceful courtyard.</string>

    <string name="tag_orthodox">Orthodox</string>


    <string name="place_33_title">Ascension Cathedral</string>
    <string name="place_33_subtitle">Historic Orthodox Cathedral</string>
    <string name="place_33_about">Ascension Cathedral is a remarkable wooden cathedral built without nails. It represents one of the finest examples of Orthodox architecture in Central Asia.</string>

    <string name="place_34_title">Central State Museum of Kazakhstan</string>
    <string name="place_34_subtitle">National History Museum</string>
    <string name="place_34_about">The Central State Museum showcases Kazakhstan’s history, culture, and археологические artifacts from ancient to modern times.</string>

    <string name="tag_museum">Museum</string>

    <string name="place_35_title">Museum of Folk Musical Instruments</string>
    <string name="place_35_subtitle">Traditional Music Museum</string>
    <string name="place_35_about">This museum presents a rich collection of traditional Kazakh musical instruments and cultural heritage exhibits.</string>

    <string name="tag_music">Music</string>
    <string name="tag_mosque">Mosque</string>
    <string name="tag_spiritual">Spiritual</string>

    <string name="place_36_title">Kasteev State Museum of Arts</string>
    <string name="place_36_subtitle">Art Museum • Fine Arts Collection</string>
    <string name="place_36_about">Kasteev State Museum of Arts is the largest art museum in Kazakhstan, featuring national and international fine art collections.</string>

    <string name="tag_art">Art</string>

    <!-- Hotels -->
    <string name="hotels_title">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotels_select">Select</string>
    <string name="hotels_check_in">Check-in</string>
    <string name="hotels_check_out">Check-out</string>
    <string name="hotels_guests">Guests</string>
    <string name="hotels_rooms">Rooms</string>
    <string name="hotels_guests_count">%1$d</string>
    <string name="hotels_rooms_count">%1$d</string>
    <string name="hotels_find">Find Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotels_recommended">Recommended</string>
    <string name="hotels_per_night">Per night</string>
    <string name="hotels_view_details">View Details</string>
    <string name="hotel_about">About</string>
    <string name="hotel_facilities">Facilities</string>
    <string name="hotel_facility_wifi">Free Wifi</string>
    <string name="hotel_facility_dining">Dining</string>
    <string name="hotel_facility_pool">Pool</string>
    <string name="hotel_facility_spa">Spa</string>
    <string name="hotel_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="hotel_location">Location</string>
    <string name="hotel_open_map">Open Map</string>
    <string name="hotel_start_from">Start from</string>
    <string name="hotel_per_night">/night</string>
    <string name="hotel_book_now">Book Now</string>
    <string name="currency_tenge">〒</string>
    <!-- Booking -->
    <string name="booking_select_room">Select Room</string>
    <string name="booking_nights">%1$d Nights</string>
    <string name="booking_guests_rooms">%1$d Guests, %2$d Room</string>
    <string name="booking_available_rooms">Available Rooms</string>
    <string name="booking_enhance_stay">Enhance Your Stay</string>
    <string name="booking_addon_per_guest">%1$s 〒 / guest</string>
    <string name="booking_addon_fixed">%1$s 〒</string>
    <string name="booking_total">Total (%1$d Nights)</string>
    <string name="booking_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="addon_royal_breakfast">Royal Breakfast</string>
    <string name="addon_vip_transfer">VIP Airport Transfer</string>
    <string name="addon_breakfast">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="addon_airport_transfer">Airport Transfer</string>
    <string name="room_deluxe_king">Deluxe King Room</string>
    <string name="room_deluxe_twin">Deluxe Twin Room</string>
    <string name="room_royal_suite">Royal Suite</string>
    <string name="room_standard">Standard Room</string>
    <string name="room_superior">Superior Room</string>
    <string name="room_executive">Executive Room</string>
    <string name="room_standard_double">Standard Double</string>
    <string name="room_superior_twin">Superior Twin</string>
    <string name="room_junior_suite">Junior Suite</string>
    <string name="room_deluxe_double">Deluxe Double</string>
    <string name="room_suite">Suite</string>
    <string name="room_classic_room">Classic Room</string>
    <string name="room_premier_twin">Premier Twin</string>
    <string name="room_wellness_suite">Wellness Suite</string>
    <string name="room_eco_room">Eco Room</string>
    <string name="room_family_room">Family Room</string>
    <string name="room_premium_cottage">Premium Cottage</string>
    <string name="room_deluxe_king_short">Deluxe King</string>
    <string name="room_club_twin">Club Twin</string>
    <string name="room_ritz_suite">Ritz Suite</string>
    <string name="room_deluxe">Deluxe</string>
    <string name="room_apartment_suite">Apartment Suite</string>
    <string name="room_classic_king">Classic King</string>
    <string name="room_club_room">Club Room</string>
    <string name="room_executive_suite">Executive Suite</string>
    <string name="addon_breakfast_buffet">Breakfast Buffet</string>
    <string name="addon_airport_shuttle">Airport Shuttle</string>
    <string name="addon_spa_package">Spa Package</string>
    <string name="addon_transfer_medeu">Transfer to Medeu</string>
    <string name="addon_club_lounge_access">Club Lounge Access</string>
    <string name="addon_heli_transfer">Heli Transfer</string>
    <string name="addon_national_breakfast">National Breakfast</string>
    <string name="addon_horse_riding">Horse Riding</string>
    <string name="addon_ski_lift_pass">Ski Lift Pass</string>
    <string name="addon_spa_day">Spa Day</string>
    <string name="addon_breakfast_incl">Breakfast Incl.</string>
    <string name="addon_wellness_breakfast">Wellness Breakfast</string>
    <string name="addon_gym_pool_access">Gym and Pool Access</string>
    <string name="room_sqm_format">%1$s m²</string>
    <string name="room_feature_king_bed">King Bed</string>
    <string name="room_feature_2_queen_beds">2 Queen Beds</string>
    <string name="room_feature_garden_view">Garden View</string>
    <string name="room_feature_city_view">City View</string>
    <string name="room_feature_mountain_view">Mountain View</string>
    <string name="room_feature_separate_living">Separate Living</string>
    <string name="room_feature_spa_access">Spa Access</string>
    <string name="room_feature_double_bed">Double Bed</string>
    <string name="room_feature_2_beds">2 Beds</string>
    <string name="room_feature_queen_bed">Queen Bed</string>
    <string name="room_feature_balcony">Balcony</string>
    <string name="room_feature_jacuzzi">Jacuzzi</string>
    <string name="room_feature_living_area">Living Area</string>
    <string name="room_feature_breakfast_incl">Breakfast Incl.</string>
    <string name="room_feature_street_view">Street View</string>
    <string name="room_feature_nature_view">Nature View</string>
    <string name="room_feature_yurt_style">Yurt Style</string>
    <string name="room_feature_private_yard">Private Yard</string>
    <string name="room_feature_club_lounge">Club Lounge</string>
    <string name="room_feature_panorama_view">Panorama View</string>
    <string name="room_feature_butler_service">Butler Service</string>
    <string name="room_feature_ski_view">Ski View</string>
    <string name="room_feature_kitchenette">Kitchenette</string>
    <string name="room_feature_forest_view">Forest View</string>
    <string name="room_feature_terrace">Terrace</string>
    <string name="room_feature_spa_bath">Spa Bath</string>
    <string name="room_feature_private_terrace">Private Terrace</string>
    <string name="room_feature_club_benefits">Club Benefits</string>
    <string name="room_feature_executive_lounge">Executive Lounge</string>
    <string name="room_feature_city_mountain_view">City And Mountain View</string>

    <string name="hotel_rixos_name">Rixos Almaty</string>
    <string name="hotel_rixos_address">Seifullin Avenue, 506</string>
    <string name="hotel_rixos_desc">Experience world-class luxury in the heart of Almaty. The Rixos Almaty Hotel offers a unique combination of comfort and traditional Kazakh hospitality. Enjoy spacious rooms, premium dining options, and a state-of-the-art spa center.</string>
    <string name="hotel_kz_name">Hotel Kazakhstan</string>
    <string name="hotel_kz_address">Dostyk Avenue, 52</string>
    <string name="hotel_kz_desc">A historic landmark in the heart of Almaty. Hotel Kazakhstan offers stunning views of the mountains and the city. Perfect blend of Soviet-era grandeur and modern comfort.</string>
    <string name="hotel_novotel_name">Novotel City Center</string>
    <string name="hotel_novotel_address">Dostyk Avenue, 104A</string>
    <string name="hotel_novotel_desc">Modern international hotel in the central business district. Novotel offers comfortable rooms, fitness center, and easy access to shopping and entertainment.</string>


    <string name="price_format">%1$s 〒</string>
    <string name="hotel_grand_aura_name">Grand Aura Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_grand_aura_address">Seifullin Avenue, 49/1</string>
    <string name="hotel_grand_aura_desc">Modern 4-star hotel in the heart of Almaty. Comfortable rooms, restaurant and fitness center. City views and convenient location popular with tourists.</string>
    <string name="hotel_royal_tulip_name">Royal Tulip Almaty</string>
    <string name="hotel_royal_tulip_address">Marat Ospanov 401/2</string>
    <string name="hotel_royal_tulip_desc">Resort hotel near Medeu. Mountain views, pool and spa. Perfect choice for relaxation.</string>
    <string name="hotel_swissotel_name">Swissôtel Wellness Resort Alatau</string>
    <string name="hotel_swissotel_address">Tau-Samaly 50A</string>
    <string name="hotel_swissotel_desc">Wellness resort in the Alatau mountains. Spa, pool and natural surroundings. Ideal for stress relief.</string>
    <string name="hotel_qazaq_auyl_name">Qazaq Auyl Eco Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_qazaq_auyl_address">Medeu Road</string>
    <string name="hotel_qazaq_auyl_desc">Eco-style resort hotel. National yurts, clean air and nature. For eco-travel lovers.</string>
    <string name="hotel_ritz_name">The Ritz-Carlton Almaty</string>
    <string name="hotel_ritz_address">Al-Farabi Avenue 77/7, Esentai Tower</string>
    <string name="hotel_ritz_desc">Luxury 5-star hotel at the foot of the Alatau mountains. Spa, pool and panoramic views. Elite retreat.</string>
    <string name="hotel_shymbulak_name">Shymbulak Resort Hotel &amp; Spa</string>
    <string name="hotel_shymbulak_address">Kerey-Zhanibek Khans 640</string>
    <string name="hotel_shymbulak_desc">Hotel at Shymbulak mountain resort. Close to the ski lift, spa and mountain views. Popular in winter and summer.</string>
    <string name="hotel_inter_name">InterContinental Almaty</string>
    <string name="hotel_inter_address">Zheltoqsan 181</string>
    <string name="hotel_inter_desc">5-star business hotel in the center, close to the mountains. Conferences, fitness and high-quality service.</string>
    <string name="wifi">wifi</string>
    <string name="dining">dining</string>
    <string name="pool">pool</string>
    <string name="spa">spa</string>
    <string name="restaurant">restaurant</string>
    <string name="gym">gym</string>
    <string name="parking">parking</string>
    <string name="ski">ski</string>
    <string name="hiking">hiking</string>
    <string name="nature">nature</string>
    <string name="fine_dining">fine_dining</string>
    <string name="fitness">fitness</string>
    <string name="business">business</string>
</resources>
